Survival Runs In Their Blood
Walking Out is a adventure, drama, thriller film directed by Alex Smith.
A city teen travels to Montana to go hunting with his estranged father, only for the
strained trip to become a battle for survival when they encounter a grizzly bear.
Cal, played by Matt Bomer.
David, played by Josh Wiggins.
Clyde, played by Bill Pullman.
Young Cal, played by Alex Neustaedter.
Lila, played by Lily Gladstone.
Richard, played by Ken White.
Walking Out is a 2017 American survival drama film directed by Alex & Andrew J.
Smith, starring Matt Bomer, and based on a short
story of the same name by David Quammen.
It was screened in the U.S.
Dramatic Competition section of the 2017 Sundance Film Festival.
It was executive produced by Rodrigo Garcia, and it
was released on October 6, 2017 by IFC.
It was filmed on location in Livingston, Paradise Valley, and Bozeman, Montana.
The film received critical acclaim.
The film explores themes of becoming an adult, parent child
relationship, montana, grizzly bear, wilderness.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.